https://www.capsugel.com/terms-conditions

Trending Now
Lonza Completes Acquisition Of Capsugel To Create Leading Integrated Solutions Provider To The Global Pharma And Consumer Healthcare Industries
Cultivate Your Probiotic Performance: Market Trends and Innovative Solutions
Terms & Conditions
Welcome to the Capsugel Website. The information provided on this site is for general informational and educational purposes only. Please read and review these Terms of Use carefully before accessing or using this website. By accessing or using this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agreed to the Terms of Use Agreement. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, you may not access or use the site.
1. Use of Website. The information provided on this site is for general informational and educational purposes. Certain sections of this website are intended for particular audiences including Capsugel's employees, customers and shareholders, as well as members of the healthcare community and the general public. Your access to and use of the information contained in the website is subject to this Terms of Use Agreement. By accessing and using this website, you accept, without limitation or qualification, this Terms of Use Agreement.
2. Content. Capsugel will use reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this website but makes no warranties or representations of any kind as to its accuracy, currency or completeness. You agree that access to and use of this website and the content thereof is at your own risk. Capsugel disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including warranties of merchantability of fitness for a particular purpose. Neither Capsugel nor any party involved in creating, producing or delivering this website shall be liable for any damages, including without limitation, direct, incidental, consequential, indirect or punitive damages, arising out of access to, use of or inability to use this website, or any errors or omissions in the content thereof. This limitation includes damages to, or for any viruses that infect, your computer equipment.
3. Indemnification. You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Capsugel, its officers, directors, employees, agents, suppliers and third party partners from and against all losses, expenses, damages and costs, including reasonable attorneys' fee, resulting from any violation by you of these Terms of Use.
4. Privacy. Capsugel respects the privacy of its website users. Please refer to Our Privacy Policy that explains users' rights and responsibilities with respect to information that is disclosed on this website.
5. Third Party Websites and Links. This website may contain links or references to other websites maintained by third parties over whom Capsugelhas no control. Such links are provided merely as a convenience. Similarly, this website may be accessed from third party links over whom Capsugel has no control. Capsugel makes no warranties or representations of any kind as to the accuracy, currency, or completeness of any information contained in such websites and shall have no liability for any damages or injuries of any kind arising from such content or information. Inclusion of any third party link does not imply an endorsement or recommendation by Capsugel.
6. Forward Looking Statements. This web site contains forward-looking statements about Capsugel's financial and operating performance, business plans and prospects, in-line products and products in development that involve substantial risks and uncertainties. Actual results could differ materially from the expectations and projections set forth in those statements. Such risks and uncertainties include, among other things, the uncertainties inherent in research and development; decisions by regulatory authorities that could affect the availability or commercial potential of Capsugel products; competitive developments; the ability to successfully market both new and existing products; challenges to the validity and enforcement of Capsugel's patents; governmental laws and regulations affecting the healthcare or nutritional supplement industries; and general economic conditions, such as interest rate and foreign currency exchange rate fluctuations. Capsugel assumes no obligation to update any forward-looking statements as a result of new information or future events or developments.
7. Non-Confidential Information. Subject to any applicable terms and conditions set forth in our Privacy Policy, any communication or other material that you send to us through the internet or post on the website by electronic mail or otherwise, such as any questions, comments, suggestions or the like, is and will be deemed to be non-confidential and Capsugel shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information. Capsugel shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such communication for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products.
8. Trademarks. All product names, whether or not appearing in large print or with the trademark symbol, are trademarks of Capsugel, its affiliates, related companies or its licensors or joint venture partners, unless otherwise noted. The use or misuse of these trademarks or any other materials, except as permitted herein, is expressly prohibited and may be in violation of copyright law, trademark law, the law of slander and libel, the law of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. Please be advised that Capsugel actively and aggressively enforces its intellectual property rights to the fullest extent of the law.
9. Copyrights. The entire contents of this website are subject to copyright protection. Copyright © 2011. The contents of this website may not be copied other than for noncommercial individual reference with all copyright or other proprietary notices retained, and thereafter may not be recopied, reproduced or otherwise redistributed. Except as expressly provided above, you may not otherwise copy, display, download, distribute, modify, reproduce, republish or retransmit any information, text or documents contained in this website or any portion thereof in any electronic medium or in hard copy, or create any derivative work based on such images, text or documents, without the express written consent of Capsugel. Nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppel or otherwise any license or right under any patent or trademark of Capsugel, or any third party.
10. Void Where Prohibited. This website and its contents are intended to comply with the laws and regulations in the U.S. Although the information on this website is accessible to users outside of the U.S., the information pertaining to Capsugel products is intended for use only by residents of the U.S. Other countries may have laws, regulatory requirements and medical practices that differ from those in the U.S.. This site links to other sites produced by Capsugel's various operating divisions and subsidiaries, some of which are outside the U.S. Those sites may have information that is appropriate only to that particular originating country. Capsugel reserves to right to limit provision of its products or services to any person, geographic region or jurisdiction and/or to limit the quantities or any products or services we provide. Any offer for any product or service made on this website is void where prohibited.
11. Governing Laws. This Terms of Use Agreement and your use of the website shall be governed by the laws of the United States of America and the State of New Jersey without regard to its conflicts of laws principles. Any legal action or proceeding related to this website shall be brought exclusively in a federal or state court of competent jurisdiction sitting in New Jersey.
12. Miscellaneous. If any provision of this Agreement is held to be unlawful, void or unenforceable, then such provision shall be severable without affecting the enforceability of all remaining provisions. Capsugel reserves the right to alter or delete materials from this website at any time at its discretion.
Copyright © 2014 Capsugel Belgium BVBA. All rights reserved
Want to learn more about Capsugel?
Contact Us
Capsugel.com Cookie Policy
Procurement Terms & Conditions
Sales Terms & Conditions
Data Transfer Policy
Privacy and Cookies Notice
Please note that Lonza has updated its Privacy Policy. By visiting our website or using services provided by Lonza, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.
We also use cookies on our websites. Cookies allow us to give you the best browsing experience and help us to understand how you use our site. You can disable cookies but parts of our website may not work. Please read our updated Cookies Policy for information about which cookies we use and the information we collect. By continuing to use this website, you agree that we may store and access cookies on your device.
By clicking "I Agree", you confirm that you are above the age of 16, that you have read and understood the Privacy Policy and the Cookies Policy, and that you agree to the collection, use and processing of your Personal Information by Lonza in accordance with said policies.
I Agree
Terms of Services
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
Sitemap
Copyright 2020
contact us
Biopharmaceuticals
